Jai Shri Krishna friends, we see that
accidents are increasing in today's time and
many people are also dying in accidents.
We can take insurance of the best amount in a very nominal amount, so
today we will
get information about it. Personal Accident Plan,
whose specialty is that for death by accident,
we have four different insurance options here:
10 lakh, 25 lakh,
50 lakh and one crore. If
death occurs due to an accident, then in that case, the
full amount of the sum assured is given to his family,
which is very helpful. At the same time,
if that person gets permanent disability, then even in
such a situation,
he gets the full amount of the sum assured, so he and
his family have financial support for the rest of his life.
Sometimes, if he gets semi-disability, two hands are gone,
two legs are gone, and his eyes are gone, then
even in such a situation, he gets complete problems.
He also gets one lakh rupees each for the expenses of the accident.
Now let's talk about a very nice benefit.  Or if
he gets disability for some time, that is, the
doctor says that he has one month of bed rest, he has
fractured, he cannot go to the office, his
salary is cut in the office, then in all these
situations, he has to sit at home for a week, but
based on the doctor's letter that he has permanent
bed rest for a certain period, then in such a
situation, up to 104 weeks, this
calculation is
given here for a person earning three to four lakh rupees annually. If he has an income more than that, then
this benefit depends on the income, so
if someone earns three to four lakh rupees annually, then he has to
sit at home for 7000 a week or a week, then
he will get 7000 from the company. If there is an insurance of 25 lakhs, then
10000, if there is an insurance of 50 lakhs, then
14000, if there is an insurance of 1 crore, then 20000. Now suppose
that a person has an insurance of 1 crore and
sits at home for a month.  If you have to stay, you will get 20 *
4 80000 rupees from the company, then this is
a very good benefit which is
called TD benefit. Its premium is
given to you below for one year, two years and three years. If we look at the premium of 10 lakhs, then
1923 rupees for one year,
3693 for two years and 5367 for three years.
Now this 5367, if we
take a premium for three years, then it becomes 14 rupees per day.
Many people use this 14 rupees for tea, snacks, cigarettes. The
premium for three years is 14 rupees
for 10 lakhs, 26 rupees for 25 lakhs, 46 rupees
for 50 lakhs and 84 rupees for one crore. That is,
we can take an accident insurance of one crore in a daily premium of less than 100 rupees
and in which
we are eligible to get this benefit. Another special
note is that this is for the earning member, that is,
if the one who is filing the ITR is the
husband, then ITR  His wife also
files ITR and even if she has an
ITR of three to four lakhs, then she is also eligible to get this. If we
talk about the death benefit, if an
accident occurs at home or at work, then
this is also covered.
We have to give the death certificate and if there is a vehicle
accident, then in such a case
we have to attach a blank FIR. In other
cases, we
can take this claim for death benefit on the basis of the death certificate and
if there is temporary disability, then on the
basis of the doctor's certificate, or if the brother is on
bed rest, then he can
get all these benefits on the basis of the doctor's certificate. So it is a very good plan.
We can also cover accident insurance with a very low premium.
So
you can contact us for information about this.  Thank you